- Good evening.
- こんばんは
- please.
- お願いします
- It's okay to come in.
- 入っても大丈夫です
- Please, please.
- どうぞどうぞ
Do you feel it?
感触するんですか?
- I like breasts.
- 胸好き
- Do you like breasts?
- 胸好き?
Breasts are for sensual purposes.
性感対応じゃん、胸
- Oh, oh, welcome.
- ああ、ああ、いらっしゃい
- Oh, welcome.
- ああ、いらっしゃい
- Good evening.
- こんばんは
- please.
- お願いします
- It's okay to come in.
- 入っても大丈夫です
Please, please come in.
どうぞどうぞ、入ってください
Well then - it's an interview.
じゃあ、 - 面接なんで
- yes.
- はい
- I have an interview right now.
- 今すぐ面接なんで
- Already?
- もうですか?
That's it already.
もうです
- Let me touch you.
- 触ってもらって
- yes.
- はい
-Okay.
- いいです
It's an interview.
面接なんで
- Is this an interview?
- これ面接ですか?
By the way, that's it.
ちなみに、あれですよ
I'm not the one doing the interview, I'm the one having the interview.
僕が面接するんじゃなくて、 僕が面接してもらう方なんで
- Am I the interviewer?
- 私が面接者ですか?
- that's right.
- そうです
- Hey, what does it feel like?
- ちょっと、どんな感じか
May I have a quick interview?
ちょっと面接してもらおうかな
- Ah, I see.
- あ、わかりました
- Well, put down your pack.
- じゃあ、パック置いて
Oh, I already put it down.
ああ、もう置いたから
- yes.
- はい
- Well then, let me have a chat with you there.
- じゃあ、そこしゃかんでもらってね
- yes.
- はい
- Do you want to take this?
- これ、とりますか?
Well then.
じゃあ
- that's right.
- そうです
Thank you for interviewing me.
面接していただいて
-
That's a nice dick.
いい おちんちです
- Nice penis?
- いいおちんち?
- Do you have a nice penis?
- いいおちんちですか
thank you.
ありがとうございます
- yes.
- はい
- Various, various, various.
- 色々、色々、色々な
I asked for various interviews.
色々な面接をしてもらってね
- yes.
- はい
- It would be nice if you could do a lot of things for me.
- 色々してもらっていいですね
First, let's look.
まず、まず見る
- look.
- 見る
- beautiful.
- きれい
- Does it look good?
- 見た目合格ですか?
- Ah, I totally passed.
- あ、全然合格です
- good.
- よかった
- That's good too.
- とっちもいいですね
- Yeah, it's pretty good though.
- ええ、それなりにいいですけどね
- Then, can I have a taste?
- じゃあ、味見してもいいですか?
- Ah, you can taste it now.
- あ、もう味見してもいいですね
- yes.
- はい
- Oh, that's kind of nice.
- あ、やさしい感じで
- It's a kind one.
- やさしい感じのやつですね
- Well then, shall we have an interview?
- じゃあ、面接しましょうか
- yes.
- はい
- Nice to meet you again.
- 改めまして
- yes.
- はい
- You know, I suddenly got a blow job.
- ね、いきなり、いきなりフェラしてもらっちゃったけど
- I agree.
- そうですね
- OK?
- 大丈夫ですか?
- yes.
- はい
- Is it okay like that?
- あんな感じでいいですか?
- yes.
- はい
- Well then, let me ask you your name.
- じゃあ、ちょっとお名前を聞こうかな
- Oh, it's Natsumi.
- あ、なつみです
- Natsumi-chan.
- なつみちゃん
- yes.
- はい
- It's cute.
- かわいいですね
Isn't it perfect?
ピチピチじゃないですか?
- No, no, no.
- いやいやいや
- how old are you?
- 何歳ですか?
- But I'm 19.
- でも、19です
- Ah, 19.
- あ、19
So, you were wearing a sailor suit just recently?
じゃあ、ね、ついこの間まで、セーラー服を着てたんですか?
- Oh, it's a blazer.
- あ、ブレザーです
- Ah, blazer.
- あ、ブレザー
Ah, a blazer.
あ、ブレザーね
Nowadays, everyone wears blazers.
今時はね、みんなブレザー
- By the way, you look really stylish.
- ちなみに、すごくスタイルがよく見えるんですけど、
How does it feel?
どんな感じですか?
Like 3 sizes.
3サイズとか
- I don't know about the 3 sizes.
- 3サイズ、分かんないんですよ
- I don't understand?
- 分かんない?
Generally speaking, what about the chest?
大体、胸は?
- Chest is C.
- 胸はCです
- C
- And what about your waist?
- で、ウエストは?
- Waist.
- ウエスト
-
It's about 50 centimeters.
50セ ンチぐらいですね
- I understand.
- 分かるんですよね
- 分かります
- What happened?
- どうしました?
- No, just a little.
- いや、ちょっと
- Did something happen?
- 何かありましたか?
- No, it's okay.
- いや、大丈夫です
- It's okay, right?
- 大丈夫ですよね
- yes.
- はい
- hey.
- ね
- By the way, what kind of school life did you have?
- ちなみに、どんな学校生活を送ってたんですか?
-
At school, I worked as a club manager.
学 校に、部活はマネージャーやってました
- Are you a club manager?
- 部活はマネージャー?
- yes.
- はい
- How many copies?
- 何部?
- It's soccer.
- サッカーです
- It looks like a soccer club.
- サッカー部っぽいよね
- He looks like a soccer club manager.
- サッカー部のマネージャーっぽいですよね
What happened?
どうしました?
- No, it's okay.
- いや、大丈夫です
- OK?
- 大丈夫ですか?
Did something happen?
何かありました?
- Please continue.
- 続けてください
- He's a bad uncle.
- 悪いおじさんだよね
Like this.
こんな風に
How did it feel?
どういう感じになったんですか?
- Does it feel good?
- いい感じですか?
- I hear boo.
- ブーって、聞こえてます
- A toy.
- おもちゃが
- Are there any toys in there?
- おもちゃ入ってますか?
When did you add that?
いつのまにそんなの入れたんですか?
- Hey, lately...
- ちょっと、最近...
- Your uncle put you in there, didn't you?
- おじさんに入れられたんだね
It can't be helped.
しょうがないですよね
- You'll be let in.
- 入れられちゃいます
- This is how you talk.
- こういう感じで話をするっていうのを
- I feel a little nervous and nervous.
- なんか、ちょっと緊張とドキドキ
- Nervous and nervous?
- 緊張とドキドキ?
- Yeah.
- うん
- Hey, can I have a look at that?
- ちょっと、それ見せてもらっていいですかね?
- yes.
- はい
- That's what it means.
- こういうことですね
What do you think?
どうですか?
- It's embarrassing.
- 恥ずかしい
- Are you embarrassed?
- 恥ずかしい?
- Does it feel good?
- 気持ちいい?
-It feels good.
- 気持ちいい
- It's embarrassing.
- 恥ずかしい
Yes, please sit down.
はい、じゃあ、座ってください
- yes.
- はい
- When you talk like this, you can learn a lot of things.
- こういう感じで話をすると、いろんなことが分かるじゃない
Is it?
ですか?
- yes.
- はい
- I wonder how it feels.
- どんな感じ方するのかな、とか
- yes.
- はい
- By the way, when did you all die?
- ちなみに、諸女はいつ亡くしたんですか?
- Ladies, uh...
- 諸女は、えっと...
- It's a small number.
- 小号ですね
- Trumpet?
- 小号?
- yes.
- はい
- What's the small number... - 12?
- 小号ってさ...- 12?
- The small number is not 12, etc.
- 小号は12じゃない、とか
Something like 11.
11とかね
- 11?
- What does that mean?
- それどういうこと?
誰、誰、誰?
- He was older.
- 年上の人でした
- How old are you?
- 何歳ぐらいの人?
- At that time it was probably 1 or 2.
- 当時が多分、1か2とか
- No, that's no good.
- ダ メじゃん、そんなの
11 is what you would call JS.
11ってさ、いわゆるJSだよね
- It's JS.
- JSですね
- It's S, right?
- Sだよね
No, I'm going to say that word.
ダメだよ、そのワード言っちゃう
- It's a golden phrase.
- 金句ですから
- It was that fast.
- そんなに早かったんだ
How was that?
どうだった、それ?
- I don't really understand it anymore.
- なんかもう、よく分かんなくって
- In the end, I made a loss, but
- 結 局、損入はしたんですけど、
- Yeah.
- うん
- I didn't go that far.
- 行くとこまではしなかったです
- Oh, that high school student.
- ああ、その高校生が
- yes.
- はい
- Oh, yeah.
- ああ、そう
You lost a lot of money, that guy.
よく損入したね、そいつ
For elementary school students.
小学生に
- That's amazing.
- すごいなあ
- Yeah.
- ええ
- What do you mean, I was like that, because I had the knowledge?
- どんな、自分はそういう、だって知識はあったわけ?
That kind of naughty thing.
そういうエッチなことの
- Or should I say, my father or something like that?
- 届くっていうか、お父さんとかが、
I would occasionally watch something like that, but
たまに見てたやつとかを見たりはしてたんですけど、
- What do you mean by AV?
- AVってこと?
- PVs, manga, etc.
- PVとか、その漫画系とか
- But what does that mean?
- でもそれがさ、ほらどういうことかっての、
Do you understand?
分かってる?
- I didn't know that at all.
- 全然知らなかったです
- Hey.
- ねえ
- So, I was 11 years old in the Showa era and I'm 19 years old now.
- で、その、じゃあ昭和11歳で今19歳だから、
- yes.
- はい
- You're quite a veteran now, aren't you?
- もうなかなかベテランじゃん、
already.
もう
- I'm not a veteran.
- ベテランではないです
- Because he's a veteran.
- だって、ベテランだよ
It's been about 8 years already, right?
もう8年くらい経ってるってことでしょ
- Oh, no, were those high school students dating?
- え、いや、その高校生はじゃあ付き合ってたの?
- No, I don't remember dating.
- いや、付き合った記憶はないですね
- I'm really interested, though.
- なんかすごい興味あるんだけど、
Why, then is it your neighbor's brother?
なんで、じゃあそれは近所のお兄さんとか?
- No, somehow, my friend was playing Ness in Love,
- いや、なんか、友達が恋するネスをやってて、
- Yeah.
- うん
- So, I want to meet the person I met,
- それでなんかその、出会った人に会いたいから、
Don't you want me to follow you?
付いてきてほしいんじゃないの?
- Go first with an escort.
- 付き添いで始めに行って
- Yeah.
- うん
- Well, we exchanged contact information.
- それで、ま、連絡先交換して、
That's what it felt like.
って感じでした
- I was able to go with you.
- 付き添いで行っていられちゃったんだ
- Hey, oh, but it's cute.
- ねえ、あ、でも可愛いからね
I guess I was just horny.
多分ムラムラしちゃったんだろうね、
That's it.
そいつね
- I'm jealous.
- 羨ましいですね
- What kind of situation is this?
- どういう場合になってますか、
now?
今?
- Can I have a look?
- ちょっと見せてもらっていいですか?
- Hey, just open your face.
- ちょっとね、顔を開いてもらって
- You've never talked like this before, right?
- こんな、こんな風にお話したことないでしょ?
- Yeah, no.
- ええ、ないです
- There isn't.
- ないのね
- I think you've taken some pretty good pictures, haven't you?
- だいぶいい感じに、撮ってきたんじゃないですか?
-
I'm looking good, you know.
私、 格好してますよ、ほら
- Let's just look at it for a moment.
- ちょっとそのまま、眺めておこう
- Can I just look at it?
- そのまま眺めておいていい?
- Are these two going together?
- この二人一緒に出る?
- Take a look, Bunri-san.
- ちょっと眺める、文理さん
- I want to see it.
- 眺めたいわ
I really want to see it.
めっちゃ眺めたいわ
- I really want to see it.
- めっちゃ眺めたい
- I was wondering what you would look like.
- どんな顔するのかなと思ったよ
- No, wait a minute, if you look at me like that.
- いや、ちょっと、そんな見られると
- Hey,
- ねえ、
It's all visible.
全部 映ってるよ
- It's hard, it's hard, it's hard.
- つらい、つらい、つらい
- tough.
- つらい
- It's tough, yes.
- つらいね、そうだね
- My jacket, let's sleep like this for a bit.
- 上着ね、ちょっとこう寝ちゃおうか
- But she has quite a lot of breasts after all.
- でも結構やっぱりおっぱい、なかなかありますね
-Do you have it?
- 持ってる?
-I have it.
- 持ってる
- Do you have it?
- 持ってるの?
-I have it.
- 持ってる
-
Are you feeling it?
感 受せいですか?
- I like breasts.
- 胸好き
- Breasts are for sensual purposes.
- 性感対応じゃん、胸
- Oh, it's cute.
- あ、かわいい
- Here it is.
- ほら、これね
- I got it, look.
- 取っちゃったよ、ほら
- There's Pyunik, look.
- ピューニックが出ちゃう、ほら
It's Punic.
ピューニックですよ
- What is it?
- どうなんですか?
Is it a folded sheet?
折り物シートですか?
- Folded sheets.
- 折り物シート
- Will there be folded items?
- 折り物が出るんですか?
- Folded items come out.
- 折り物が出る
- Doesn't it make the folded sheet look squishy?
- 折り物シートビチビチになっちゃうじゃないですか?
- I don't have to
- ないちゃ
cormorant.
う
- Huh?
- あれ?
- There's no excuse.
- おケケがないですね
- It's smooth.
- つるつるですね
- It's getting smaller.
- ひとくちょになってますね
As expected of a veteran.
さすがベテランですね
- Kire
- きれ
stomach.
い
beautiful.
き れい
- Look.
- ほら
- So it turned out like this.
- こういうようになったんですね
- I like what you're saying.
- 言ってるのが好きなんだね
- It's okay, Yuki-san.
- いいんだよ、ゆきさん
- Did you say that?
- 言っちゃったんですか?
- Hey, can I jump around for a second?
- ちょっと、おれさん、ぴょろぴょろしてもいいですか?
- yes.
- はい
- picture?
- え?
- Yeah.
- うん
- I'm going to jump around.
- ぴょろぴょろするよ
- There were a lot of what-ifs.
- もしもがいっぱい出てきましたよ
- So, can I pet you?
- じゃあ、かわいがってもっていいですか?
- Yeah.
- うん
- Hey, Micchan.
- ちょっと、みっちゃんさん
- Yeah.
- うん
-Would you like to play around with your pet?
- ペットでぴょろぴょろしてくれる?
- Yeah.
- う ん
- hey.
- ね
- Let's finally go.
- やっといこうね